<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musicians of the San Antonio Symphony</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Musicians of the San Antonio Symphony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 15:23:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Arts and the Economy: The Numbers Show</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/article/numbers-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 15:23:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/article/numbers-show/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;economic-impact-of-nonprofit-arts-culture-organization:1465e6b7307bf0f1e92270462c790e51&#34;&gt;Economic Impact of Nonprofit Arts &amp;amp; Culture Organization&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonprofit arts and culture organizations are valuable contributors to the business community. They are employers, producers, consumers, and key promoters of their cities and regions. Nonprofit arts and culture organization spending in 2005 was an estimated $63.1 billion. &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arts and the Economy: What The Experts Say</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/article/experts-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 15:14:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/article/experts-say/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my own philanthropy and business endeavors, I have seen the critical role that the arts play in stimulating creativity and in developing vital communities&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash; &lt;cite&gt;Paul G. Allen, Philantropist and Co-Founder of Microsoft&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arts and Education, the Facts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/article/arts-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 15:03:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/article/arts-impact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nearly ALL San Antonio Symphony musicians mentor music students&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brian Santero</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/musician/Brian-Santero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 01:06:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/musician/Brian-Santero/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Brian is Principal Trombone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>second</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 21:26:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/second/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Second post.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 12:07:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Testing the markdown.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 11:14:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The musicians of the San Antonio Symphony believe our orchestra is a vital cultural icon, an integral source of identity for our city and a public trust. Economically, the Symphony helps define San Antonio as a major metropolitan area with the highest quality musical culture, making it more attractive to tourists and potential businesses alike. Artistically and educationally, we are integrated into the fabric of life through the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The San Antonio Symphony is the only full-time, professional, performing arts organization in San Antonio. Each member of the orchestra is a highly-trained musician; 75% of us have Masters degrees in our fields that are the culmination of a musical training that begins in early childhood. Each position in the orchestra is filled through rigorous and intense international competition. The orchestra&amp;rsquo;s musicians come from as close as San Antonio and as far away as Syria, Turkey, China, and Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as importantly, we live here - 60% of us are homeowners - raise our families here and pay taxes here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We serve as positive role models for countless San Antonio youth. At last count, 90% of the members of the orchestra were mentoring around 800 individual students in one-on-one private lessons.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>